[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What food is a rich source of vitamin B6?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Meat", "Vegetables", "Nuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Silkie chicken is the newest known breed.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2005 remake of The House of Wax, the wax museum was located in the real town of Ambrose, Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Rowan Atkinson major in at the Newcastle University", "correct_answer": "Electrical engineering", "incorrect_answers": ["Economics", "Art", "Chemistry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the timid assistant to the heroes in every Star Wars film?", "correct_answer": "C-3P0", "incorrect_answers": ["Battle Droid", "Storm trooper", "R-4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first European to see The Bronx, NY?", "correct_answer": "Henry Hudson", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Hutchinson", "Jonas Bronck", "Jonas Valerian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Choose the correct ordering of these medical jobs abbreviations, in increasing order of salary.", "correct_answer": "MA, LPN, RN, PA, MD", "incorrect_answers": ["MA, LPN, PA, RN, MD", "MA, PA, LPN, RN, MD", "LPN, MD, PA, MA, RN"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "No animals or plants live in the Dead Sea .", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character, portrayed by Ilse Steppat, is Blofelds henchwoman in On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Irma Bunt", "incorrect_answers": ["Heidi  Werkmeister", "Kirsten  Klotz", "Lorelei Oberst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These animals are usually monogamous and both parents take care of their young.", "correct_answer": "Swans", "incorrect_answers": ["Hedgehogs", "All of these", "Wolves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Midnight Run, what actor portrayed Law Vegas gangster Jimmy Serrano?", "correct_answer": "Dennis Farina", "incorrect_answers": ["Harvey Keitel", "Kareem  Ofwheat", "Dennis Franz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The square root of a number is always smaller than that number.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]